LoganAlleyne

Web Developer

Contact







About

I am passionate about creating beautiful and accessible user experiences, striving to find the perfect balance of aesthetics and usability while writing clear and easy to maintain code.

My goal is that if anyone interacts with something I've made they'll be happy, whether they're the user or a developer. It is also important to me that my work has a positive impact on the world in some way.

Education ____

Computing for Digital Media (BSc hons) University of Sussex

Modules include:
Web 3D Applications,
Human-Computer
Interaction, Technology
Enhanced Learning,
and Software
Engineering.

BTEC Level 3 Extended Diploma IT

A two year A-level equivalent IT course

Skills_

Technology

HTML Vue GitHub
CSS & SCSS Vuex/Pina XML
TailwindCSS Nuxt REST APIs
JavaScript Node Vite
TypeScript Laravel Vitest

Experience

Technical Production Manager BrandStencil | Hove | Feburary 2021 - Present

Working on a charity focused templating & brand management SaaS. I am responsible for all template output. Building the vast majority personally and overseeing the hire, management, and output of freelancers & temporary team members when needed. Working with QA and Project Managers to ensure consistent, high quality, pixel perfect, dynamic templates with a very strong focus on UX and accessibility.

Software

Creative cloud

VS Code

Illustrator

InDesign Postman

Photoshop

I am also responsible for maintaining and developing the front end of the application, designing & building new features, interpreting and implementing both internal and external requests, and improving the existing application's UX and accessibility.

Technology: HTML, SCSS, Tailwind. PHP, Laravel, Blade, JavaScript Vue, Vuex, REST APIs, XPath, XML, JSON, YAML, Docker, MySQL

Junior Product Developer ReedPop | Brighton | July 2020 - December 2020

Working as a Junior Front-end web developer I maintained and updated an array of different sites, including Eurogamer.net and RockPaperShotgun.com. I also helped to build all new digital events sites for very large digital only events such as PAX x EGX for which we had over 12 million impressions.

Technology: Django, Python, Wordpress, PHP, Docker

Technical Operator The Edit_ | Brighton | September 2019 - July 2020

Working in television post-production, helping with assistant editing and technical support, with a broad number of responsibilities and a variety of challenges daily in a high pressure environment as part of a small highly collaborative team.

Technology: Avid Media Composer & NEXIS, PC Hardware, Networking